in this fastpaced world often people are
burdened with the many financial and
emotional worries to top that they live
a sedentary
lifestyle these factors make them prone
to Major Medical events often termed as
critical illness such illnesses and
accidents can have an adverse impact on
one's finances an unfortunate death or
disability or even hospitalization due
to such events might affect an
individual's ability to meet his
financial liabilities such as serving a
loan or meeting day-to-day expenses to
cater to such customer needs go for
ICICI Lombard's critty Shield plus a
plan that ensures that protection
doesn't stop it helps you during any
major or minor illnesses or major
surgeries covered under the policy or if
you meet with an accident icic Lombard's
critty Shield plus comes with many key
benefits such as coverage for 92
critical Ines coverage for 106 surgical
procedures cancerous store benefit
multiple pay for critical illness 92
major and minor critical illnesses are
covered by this plan this is a severity
based payout it covers 100% for major
critical illnesses and 25% for minor
critical illnesses which are classified
into cancer and blood disorders heart
and blood vessels major organs nervous
system other illnesses the best part is
there is no waiting period between
claims and that's not all critty Shield
plus also provides optional coverage for
106 surgical procedures the severity
based payout is 100% for major surgery
and 50% for minor surgery this plan also
offers cancer restore benefit so you
will be eligible to claim under this
benefit provided you renew this policy
subject to having received the premium
for the cancer and blood disorders
bucket and cancer restore benefit as per
the original sum insured at the time of
renewal when illnesses are on the rise
it's better to stay additionally
protected the multiple pay for critical
illness option allows you to claim from
major and minor Bucket from each of the
five critical illness buckets in times
like these don't wait for a
life-threatening or critical illness to
strike and you plan for it and
protect yourself and your family today
with ICICI Lombards pretty Shield plus
not only are you covered for a major
exigency but you can also count on quick
and easy in-house claim processing with
24/7 support from our experts